<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="40">
  <author>yumi</author>
  <version>1.3.0.0</version>
  <contributors>yumi, mrbear, jujuokl, alpha117</contributors>
  <title>
    <en>ContractorMod</en>
    <de>ContractorMod</de>
    <fr>Mod ETA</fr>
  </title>
  <description>
    <en><![CDATA[
    This mod enable simulating a defined number of characters you control one by one during a solo game.

    ==== CHANGELOG ====
    Fixed in v1.3.0.x
     - onFoot character is inclined when looking up or down
    New in v1.3.0.0
     - Porting mod to FS19
    ==== KNOWN ISSUES ====
     - When passengers in a vehicle, worker is not stopped when driver exits => https://github.com/yumi-modding/FS17_ContractorMod/issues/15
     - Incab passenger camera is same camera than incab driver camera => https://github.com/yumi-modding/FS17_ContractorMod/issues/20

    By default, 4 characters are available Alex, Barbara, Chris and David.
    At first loading of a map, they are located at the Career starting point.
    When saving the game, characters location and vehicle is saved so they will be restored when next loading the game.
    So you will be able to continue your game exactly as you left it.

    Default keys to switch between characters are:
    - NEXT    : Tab
    - PREVIOUS: Shift + Tab
    They can be changed but by default they replaced the standard switch between vehicles since it's disable.

    This mod is compatible with CoursePlay and FollowMe mods.
    So, for example, when using FollowMe, one character will be the Leader and another one the Follower.
    Characters can be seen on the minimap when activating default category (the last one represented by a house) in the map overview screen.

    Name, gender, color and number of characters can be changed in ContractorMod.xml file for new games.
    Once a game has been saved, they can be changed in ContractorMod.xml file present in related savegame folder.
    ContractorMod.xml file also contains configuration for passengers for mods vehicles. You can add your own mods here.
    ]]></en>
    <de><![CDATA[
    Dieser Mod ermöglicht das Simulieren einer definierten Anzahl von Charakteren, die du während eines Solospiels einzeln kontrollierst.

    ==== CHANGELOG ====
    Fixed in v1.3.0.x
     - onFoot character is inclined when looking up or down
    New in v1.3.0.0
     - Porting mod to FS19
    ==== KNOWN ISSUES ====
     - When passengers in a vehicle, worker is not stopped when driver exits => https://github.com/yumi-modding/FS17_ContractorMod/issues/15
     - Incab passenger camera is same camera than incab driver camera => https://github.com/yumi-modding/FS17_ContractorMod/issues/20

    Standardmäßig sind 4 Charaktere verfügbar: Alex, Barbara, Chris und David.
    Beim ersten Laden einer Karte befinden sie sich am Karrierestartpunkt.
    Beim Speichern des Spiels werden der Standort des Charakters und das Fahrzeug gespeichert, damit sie beim nächsten Laden des Spiels wiederhergestellt werden.
    So können Sie Ihr Spiel genauso fortsetzen, wie Sie es verlassen haben.

    Standardschlüssel zum Umschalten zwischen Zeichen sind:
    - NÄCHSTER: Tab
    - ZURÜCK: Umschalt + Tab
    Sie können geändert werden, aber standardmäßig ersetzen sie den Standard-Switch zwischen Fahrzeugen, da er deaktiviert ist.

    Dieser Mod ist kompatibel mit CoursePlay und FollowMe Mods.
    So wird zum Beispiel bei der Verwendung von FollowMe ein Charakter der Leader und ein weiterer der Follower sein.
    Charaktere können auf der Minikarte gesehen werden, wenn die Standardkategorie (die letzte durch ein Haus repräsentiert) im Kartenübersichtsbildschirm aktiviert wird.
    
    Name, Geschlecht, Farbe und Anzahl der Zeichen können in der ContractorMod.xml Datei für neue Spiele geändert werden.
    Sobald ein Spiel gespeichert wurde, kann es in der Datei "ContractorMod.xml" geändert werden, die im zugehörigen Spielstandordner vorhanden ist.
    ContractorMod.xml Datei enthält auch die Konfiguration für Passagiere für Mods Fahrzeuge. Sie können hier Ihre eigenen Mods hinzufügen.
    ]]></de>
    <fr><![CDATA[
    Ce mod permet de simuler un nombre défini de personnages différents durant une partie solo que vous controlez tour à tour.

    ==== CHANGELOG ====
    Fixed in v1.3.0.x
     - onFoot character is inclined when looking up or down
    New in v1.3.0.0
     - Porting mod to FS19
    ==== PROBLEMES CONNUS ====
     - Lorsqu'un passager est dans un véhicule, l'ouvrier ne s'arrete pas quand le conducteur quitte le véhicule => https://github.com/yumi-modding/FS17_ContractorMod/issues/15
     - La caméra intérieure du passager est la même que celle du conducteur => https://github.com/yumi-modding/FS17_ContractorMod/issues/20

    Par défaut, 4 personnages sont disponibles Alex, Barbara, Chris et David.
    Au premier chargement d'une map ils sont positionnés au point de départ de la map.
    Dès la première sauvegarde, les positions/véhicules des perso sont sauvegardés et seront rechargés au prochain chargement.
    Vous pouvez ainsi reprendre la partie exactement là où vous l'avez laissé.

    Les touches par défaut pour passer d'un perso à l'autre sont:
    - SUIVANT   : Tab
    - PRECEDENT : Shift + Tab
    Ces touches peuvent être personnalisées et remplacent le switch standard de véhicules qui est désactivé dans le mod.

    Ce mod est compatible avec les mods CoursePlay et FollowMe.
    Ainsi, en mode FollowMe par exemple, un perso sera le Leader et un autre perso le Follower.
    Les perso sont visibles sur la minimap lorsque la catégorie par défaut (la dernière représentée par une maison) est activée dans la vue Aperçu de la carte.

    Le nom, le genre, la couleur et le nombre de perso peuvent être modifiés dans le fichier ContractorMod.xml pour les nouvelles parties.
    Une fois la partie sauvegardée, les modifications se font dans le fichier ContractorMod.xml du répertoire de sauvegarde habituel (savegame..).
    Le fichier ContractorMod.xml contient aussi la configuration des passagers pour les véhicules mods. Vous pouvez ajoutez vos propres mods ici.
    ]]></fr>
  </description>
  <iconFilename>images/ContractorMod.dds</iconFilename>

  <l10n filenamePrefix="modDesc_l10n" /> <!-- Load the corresponding modDesc_l10n_<language>.XML file, or revert to 'en'/'de'. -->

  <extraSourceFiles>
    <sourceFile filename="scripts/ContractorMod.lua" />
    <sourceFile filename="scripts/ContractorModWorker.lua" />
  </extraSourceFiles>
  
  <inputBindings>
    <input name="ContractorMod_NEXTWORKER" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_tab" key2="" button="" device="0" mouse="" />
    <input name="ContractorMod_PREVWORKER" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lshift KEY_tab" key2="" button="" device="0" mouse="" />
    <input name="ContractorMod_WORKER1" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lctrl KEY_1" key2="" button="" device="0" mouse="" />
    <input name="ContractorMod_WORKER2" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lctrl KEY_2" key2="" button="" device="0" mouse="" />
    <input name="ContractorMod_WORKER3" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lctrl KEY_3" key2="" button="" device="0" mouse="" />
    <input name="ContractorMod_WORKER4" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lctrl KEY_4" key2="" button="" device="0" mouse="" />
    <input name="ContractorMod_WORKER5" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lctrl KEY_5" key2="" button="" device="0" mouse="" />
    <input name="ContractorMod_WORKER6" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lctrl KEY_6" key2="" button="" device="0" mouse="" />
    <input name="ContractorMod_WORKER7" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lctrl KEY_7" key2="" button="" device="0" mouse="" />
    <input name="ContractorMod_WORKER8" category="ONFOOT VEHICLE" key1="KEY_lctrl KEY_8" key2="" button="" device="0" mouse="" />
   </inputBindings>  
</modDesc>
